!
Yay, pancakes!
So first thing off my bucket list, having American pancakes in a breakfast diner basically.
and I hope they taste as good as they look.
Alright, we're on our way to a supermarket here in Miami.
First time being in the US for me.
So I know everything about the US from TV shows and movies, obviously.
a lot of cliches, probably a lot of stupid stuff. But now I'm here to see it myself and today we
already had breakfast which was really delicious and now I said I want to check out a car. No,
I want to check out a supermarket to see all the crazy stuff they're selling here. Maybe tonight
I'll have a look at the city here in Miami because I've not been to Miami Beach yet.
so it's going to be exciting
So I'm back at the hotel after the grocery store and I noticed that it's
really expensive the food compared to German prices and the yeah the cliche
about the packaging the huge sizes and a lot of plastic is true and then we
wanted to find a liquor store and it was an odyssey we walked for three kilometers
and we found it in the end and we bought some drink a little one a little one a
little bottle of vodka and I have to say Starbucks coffee and alcohol are like
almost cheaper than in Germany and yeah so apparently we have to live from
coffee and alcohol. That's fine for me.
Your lips and my throat, your hands on mine, on mine
Two bodies together, the ins and the ins
The pain and the pleasure, the two mortals in
How would you know what I'm thinking of?
To me, the last can be as beautiful as love
It's the night, you feel pure heart and soul
So I'm at the pool area of my hotel for the last two nights because I'm flying back to Germany tomorrow
So now I guess I'm going to meet up with the girls from Germany again to like
grab something to eat and explore the city a bit more
I have to explore Miami Beach because I haven't been here really. By the way, don't mind my dark circles because we had some
hard party nights at the cruise. No, we had an amazing time and I did not get that much sleep
but it was fun so when I go to bars or restaurants I see the prices but then
they keep adding stuff
which is really weird and it gets me so confused but anyway let's go and have a
stroll around the city
And clutched at her breast
I thought she was coming
I'd never have guessed that
As she prevailed
As white as a flower
She collapsed to the floor
And was dead in an hour
Oh, dear.
I'm there
You're there
Okay, so last night in Miami
I'm here at my hotel room
I'm sharing it with four girls
which is always fun
because you get to know people
What was not fun is the weather
so yesterday evening and today
it's like stormy, rainy
rainy and not what I expected to be honest because we wanted to do beach days but it's fine
I'll have to catch my flight later on so here is my quick yeah final impression of being in the US
for a week for the first time people are really nice I like that and of course the weather
I love palm trees so Miami is a really cool spot for that but there's always air conditioning
everywhere like in shops in hallways in hotels it's really cold I was freezing
sometimes when we went out for dinner it's like why is it so cold I've been
taking uber around a lot which is really cool it's that common here but cars on
the street they're like SUVs really huge cars like the total stereotype you know
from America and no one is walking everyone is driving Miami has a really
bad public transport system so you have to basically take an uber by the way
I've written everything down here and I mean food is most of the time really
really sweet or really really salty it's hard to come by healthy food I do love
the cookies though they're great so yeah I'll catch up with the girls now and
then head to the airport in the afternoon it was a really fun time here
I totally enjoyed it. Maybe I'll be back, we'll see. It won't probably be my last time in the US,
so see you around in the next video. I hope you enjoyed this one.